Speaker 1: It.
Speaker 1: Jumping on.
Speaker 1: Daniel wanted just to kind of for you to be able to meet the team real quickly and then kind of hear at a high level, you know, what we're looking for.
Speaker 1: Like I said, you know, a lot of stuff that you need to do in your sleep, like it's nothing crazy and just kind of get your thoughts on.
Speaker 1: On some of this, then also kind of just get started.
Speaker 1: We can.
Speaker 1: Oh, gosh.
Speaker 1: I did a whole really good spiel and I was on mute.
Speaker 1: All right, I'll start over.
Speaker 1: Anyway, I got.
Speaker 1: I got.
Speaker 1: I got Lana sitting here kind of with me and Alec and Alex.
Speaker 1: K. Also part of the green.
Speaker 1: Martin, appreciate you jumping on.
Speaker 1: Daniel wanted just to kind of for you to be able to meet the team real quickly and then kind of hear at a high level, you know, what we're looking for.
Speaker 1: Like I said, you know, I think a lot of this stuff, like even Luke can do in your sleep, like it's nothing.
Speaker 1: Nothing crazy and just kind of get your thoughts on.
Speaker 1: On some of this and then also kind of just get started.
Speaker 1: We're excited to have some of these capabilities.
Speaker 1: Okay, I'll let Lis.
Speaker 1: Do you want to introduce kind of yourself of real quickly turn and Luke also, so that Lus and Alex haven't had a real chance to.
Speaker 1: To kind of meet you and kind of hear about your.
Speaker 1: Kind of your background.
Speaker 2: Sure, no problem.
Speaker 2: Take it away for just a few seconds.
Speaker 2: Hi, guys.
Speaker 2: I'm Daniel, director of AI here at EIC.
Speaker 2: And I've known William hallway for, gosh, almost 20 years.
Speaker 2: Seems like he and I must Admit, back in 2007, I think it was.